getbowtied.com 2016-10-08

# Privacy Policy | Get Bowtied

**Welcome!**  
Thanks for your interest in Get Bowtied. Please read this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service as you must agree to both documents in order to have permission to use our service (including our WordPress themes). This privacy policy describes how www.getbowtied.com and other related pages collect and use your personal information. We reserve the right to change and modify the privacy policy at any time without any prior notice. Please review this policy periodically.

**Data**  
You can visit visit www.getbowtied.com or other pages related to this website without voluntarily sharing personal information. However, if you want to communicate with us or subscribe to newsletter, you will need to reveal certain personal information.

We collect contact information such as name, email addresses of those who communicate with us via email, purchase code or user name, preferences information (i.e product interests), information shared voluntarily by clients such as survey information or personal messages sent by clients (such as ratings, reviews and feedback), usage activity (what pages users visit, purchase history). We also collect non-identifying information such as IP address, referring URL, browser type, operating system etc, but we do not connect any of the personal information with the non-personal data.

We use the information we collect in order to respond to user requests, improve user experience and our products, the content of our websites, our marketing efforts and generally, the quality of our service. We do not sell this data to other companies for commercial purposes unless we have reasons to believe release is appropriate to comply with the law or information is needed to investigate or take action regarding illegal activities such as fraud, potential threats to the physical safety of any person and violations of the Terms and Conditions.

**Cookies**  
We use cookies to identify and track visitors, their usage of the site and their site access preferences. In addition, we use cookies to help run online marketing campaigns and track ads.  
Users who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should disable cookies in their browsers. However, some features of the site may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Consent**  
If you do not agree with the collection or use of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to Get Bowtied.
